[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "P.J. Crowley, are we heading to any kind of nuclear conflict with North Korea here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I really don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["P.J. Crowley"], "LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "At what point should the United States consider some kind of military attack, albeit from a defensive standpoint if we can't put up with these saber rattling threats any longer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "I think we need to be careful there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Should China be doing more to get North Korea to put a cork on it, to put it bluntly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I think -- I think -- Piers, you're exactly right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China", "North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "How far could they reach?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "ROWLEY: Well, they have a nuclear capability.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Why did you retract it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I did retract is because after rereading it and then, you know, hearing from you and other people say, maybe it was a bit crass to use that word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "ORGAN: Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "I have friends together 40 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Do you agree to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "You are linking --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Do you agree to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Let me tell you what I don't agree with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Do you understand why gay people -- why gay people find that particularly offensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NN", "NNS", ":", "WRB", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "But it's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Where does it stop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Let me talk about redefinition of marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Where does it stop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "You've raised a good point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "What is your answer to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Those are laws that were made by man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "You said ultimately it's about changing the culture of the country, it inevitably lead to teaching our public school kids that gay marriage is a perfectly fine alternative and no different -- why shouldn't they be taught that gay marriage is a perfectly fine alternative?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I don't think it's a perfectly fine alternative.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Hmm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Same-sex marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Is it a crime against nature?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "I'm not going to get into if it's a crime against nature, whatever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Pretty shocking stuff from Michael Reagan, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Reagan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "It just annoys people, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "So it's not as bad as we think, this guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "No, sir, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "I mean, this is unusual behavior, even by sporting coach standards, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "ORGAN: I mean did -- did other players feel that he went too far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "And how would he react if anyone tried to stand up to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "You know, he would get into, you know, heated argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Was he ever homophobic when you were playing in terms of the way he spoke to players and was he ever racist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "No, sir, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Did he motivate you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, I felt that he was -- he was viewed in a -- in a wrong manner.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson", "Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Valerie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, even if he deviated from the standard of care, he didn't cause the death of Michael Jackson because on the night Michael Jackson died, he was not on a propofol drip.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Did you read the toxicology?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "He had propofol in every single of the eight specimens, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "That's correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray", "Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What was expected of Conrad Murray, and is it true that it was AEG paying Conrad Murray directly, not Michael Jackson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "First of all, I'd like to point out that Conrad Murray never received a dime for caring for Michael Jackson.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"], "PERSON": ["Conrad Murray", "Conrad Murray", "Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"], "PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Isn't a doctor paid -- if you render services for two months, aren't you paid for those services if your patient dies and suddenly you aren't -- you don't get paid for the two months that you took care of a patient?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "But that becomes an issue of litigation between Conrad Murray and AEG, I guess.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Well, Tom, I mean -- Tom, from a legal point of view, that e- mail is going to be pretty significant, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "-NONE-", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Very significant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "And you'd lost your left leg and nearly died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "And he's a drummer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "When this accident happened, did you both feel that this could be it, that you were going to die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "I was behind him 10 feet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "How is the leg?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "The leg is wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Christmas Day"]}, "docId": "130403pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "$6 million man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "The leg is a -- every hour it feels like, you know, it's Christmas Day to me right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$6 million"]}}]